

# ALI SAJJAD

## **SECONDARY PROPERTY AGENT REAL ESTATE**

# **RESUME OBJECTIVE**

Insightful sales associate with 5+ years of professional experience in online and print media. Eager to boost DEF Inc's revenue by at least 40% over the next fiscal year. In previous positions, exceeded quarterly sales targets by 10% every quarter. Maintained a customer retention rate of 90% YOY thanks to which won Salesman of the Year Award in 2021.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2019 - 2022

Dynamic companies

## **SALESMAN**

The Sales Representative is responsible for selling products and meeting customer needs while obtaining orders from existing or potential sales outlets. They ensure that the customer is satisfied and adequately taken care of while making a purchase. This way, they can establish new accounts for their employer.

2015 - 2017

Toyota showroom

## **SALES EXECUTIVE**

Submits orders by referring to price lists and product literature.

Keeps management informed by submitting activity and results reports, such as daily call reports, weekly work plans, and monthly and annual territory analyses.

2017 - 2022

Sultan Developer

#### **PROPERTY BROKER**

5 Years experience in property dealing in Pakistan Defence Housing Authority Lahore Union Developer, National Developer, Central Park, Defence Housing Authority Islamabad, Defence Housing Authority Multan, Defence Housing Authority Bahawalpur, Bahira Town Lahore, Bahira Town Islamabad, Bahira Town Karachi, Lake City, Park view City, Defence Housing Authority Peshawar,

2023 - 2024

Alfa Real State

#### **PROPERTY BROKER**

1 Years experience in property dealing in UAE Randhawa Real State.

1 Year experience in property dealing in UAE Alfa Real Estate

# **CONTACT**

Email:

theonegroup.pk@gmail.com

**Phone:** +971 50 296 6962

Address: AL satwa Dubai.U-A-E

# **PERSONAL**

Name : ALI SAJJAD

Date of Birth: 05 OCT 1998

Gander : Male

Marital Status: Married

Nationality : Pakistani

Religion : Islam

Visa Status : Own Visa

Passport No: GX5574951

# **SKILLS**

**Problem Solving** 

Adaptability

Collaboration

Strong Work Ethic

Time Management

Critical Thinking

Handling Pressure

## **EDUCATION**

2013

Metric in computer science Govt Model High School

2015